https://www.nats.org/privacy.html

Privacy Policy
NATS respects your privacy and is committed to protecting your personal information. It is important for you to understand what information we collect about you, and what we do with it:
1. What information do we collect and what do we do with it?
We do not collect personally identifiable information about you, except when you provide it to us. For example, if you complete a registration form, you may be asked to provide certain information such as: name, e-mail and mailing address. We may also collect your credit card details if you choose this payment option when purchasing any of our products and services.
The amount of personally identifiable information that a member chooses to disclose to the Association is completely up to the member. The minimum information required to maintain membership is a member's first name, last name and valid email address. Members wishing to resign membership may request their personal information be completely deleted from our membership records.The information you supply will be used to provide you with the requested information and/or service. It may also be used to deliver other communications containing pertinent NATS product updates and information. If you prefer not to receive such communications, you may opt-out by sending an email to , subject line titled "opt-out".We may collect, store or accumulate certain non-personally identifiable information concerning your use of this Website, such as: which of our pages are most popular, etc.We do not sell, rent, or give-away your personal information to any third parties.
2. Cookies and Log Files
We may place a "cookie" on your computer's hard drive so we can recognize you as a return user and personalize your experience. A cookie is a piece of data that enables us to track and target your preferences. The cookie will be stored on your computer's hard drive until you remove it. We may also use temporary or "session" cookies to help you shop. These cookies will expire when you leave the Website. You can have your browser notify you of, or automatically reject, cookies. If you reject our cookies, you may still use our Website, but you may be limited in the use of some of the features.In addition, we may use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer our Website, track traffic patterns, and gather demographic information for aggregate use, as well as for credit fraud protection and risk reduction. Except as otherwise disclosed in this Privacy Policy, we will not use IP addresses in combination with your personally identifiable information.
3. Security and Safeguards
We implement various security measures to protect the security of your personal information, both on and off line. In the case of online transactions, credit card numbers are only ever transmitted using secure connections, and are never stored on our servers. If you have any questions about security at our Website, you can send an email to .
4. Links
This Website may contain links to or from other websites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of other websites. This Privacy Policy applies only to the information we collect on this Website.
5. Comments
We have taken great measures to ensure that your visit to our Website is an excellent one and that your privacy is constantly respected. If you have any questions, comments or concerns about our privacy practices or website, please contact us at .
About Us
Membership
Competitions
Programs
Events
Store
About Us
Board of Directors
NATS Artist Awards (NATSAA)
Pre-Conference Workshop: Pop/Rock Vocalism for the Music Theater Singer
Pre-Conference Workshop: The Aging Voice
Pre-Conference Workshop: Training the Singer and the Teacher
Stephen Smith Master Class
Schedule - Saturday, July 9
Breakout Session: Do We Hallucinate Vowels?
Breakout Session: Why Would I Want to Occlude Anything?
Breakout Session: Stepping on Stage: Casting in the East, Midwest and West
Breakout Session: Making Our Garden Grow, Cultivating 21st-Century Art Song
Breakout Session: You’ve Got a Business, Teaching Singing
Breakout Session: Let's Get Moving! - Body Mapping Activities
Breakout Session: Vocal Health on Broadway & Beyond
Breakout Session: Assessment Tools for Applied Voice Teachers
Breakout Session: NATS Talks
Breakout Session: Collaborative Coaching with Warren Jones
Master Class with Renée Fleming
Renée Fleming Q & A
Publisher Showcase: Imagine Music Together in Your Community
Breakout Session: Reinventing the Female Classical Voice After Menopause
Breakout Session: NATS Books
Master Class with Warren Jones
Plenary Session: Choral Singing from the Conductor's Podium
Breakout Session: Ladies of Lyric and Song - Female Composers and Lyricists
Breakout Session: What is Intonation?
Breakout Session: Kinesthesia of Singing - Science in Action
Breakout Session: Sharpening the Saw: High– & Low–Tech Wellness Strategies
Breakout Session: The Art of Being a Great Adjudicator
Publisher Showcase: The Voice Curriculum of The Royal Conservatory
Breakout Session: Bringing the Song To Life - It's a Matter of Style
Breakout Session: Habilitating the Injured Singer - a Systematic Approach
Breakout Session: Accessible Publication
Plenary Session: Voice Science with Dr. Robert Bastian (Session I)
Plenary Session: Voice Science with Dr. Robert Bastian (Session II)
Breakout Session: Comedy in Song - Humorous Art-Songs in English
Breakout Session: Singing Seniors - Restoring the Aging Singer
Breakout Session: Rocking The Traditional Singing Boat
Breakout Session: Big is Beautiful - Support for Large Voices
Breakout Session: Expanding Your Independent Studio
Publisher Showcase: Bold and Brave - Arts Songs for the 21st Century
Publisher Showcase: Online Practice Room for Singers, Teachers, Schools
Breakout Session - A Developmental Look at SINGING: It’s Never Too Late or
Breakout Session - Collaborative Pianist Panel Discussion
Breakout Session - Practical Guide for Working with Voice Disorders
Breakout Session - A Career Guide for the Professional Chorister
Voice Science Sessions
Publisher Showcase - Broadway Stars Sing Sondheim
Publisher Showcase - New Materials from Inside View Press
2012 NATSAA Winner Concert
Breakout Session - The Performer Within: A Movement-Based Performance Pedag
Breakout Session - Beyond Communication: Using Lyric Diction
Breakout Session - Training “Mr. Soprano” and “Ms. Tenor”
Breakout Session - Valuing the Voice of Diversity
Breakout Session - American Art Song: Major Trends of the Past 100 Years
Plenary Session - Stepping On Stage - Pop/Rock Music Theater
Master Class - Lunch with Andrew Lippa
Publisher Showcase - A Taste of Estill Voice Training
Plenary Session - Master Class with Margo Garrett
Breakout Session - Standard Pedagogy and Technique for Female Belt Voice
Breakout Session - Women Teaching Men
Breakout Session - Facing Forward/Looking Back
Breakout Session - Vocal Landmines
Breakout Session - Informed Copyright Behavior
Publisher Showcase - MusicalTheaterSongs.com - The Right Song, Right Now
Breakout Session - A Lifetime of Singing: Choral/Vocal Techniques
Breakout Session - CCM Voice Pedagogy and the Singing Voice Teacher
Breakout Session - Special Needs Panel
Plenary Session - Master Class with Thomas Hampson
Publisher Showcase - Resonance - A Comprehensive Voice Series
Publisher Showcase - Discover Music Together Family Classes
Plenary Session - Thomas Hampson Lecture and Q&A
Breakout Session - The ‘Screen Invasion’
Breakout Session - The Dynamic Classroom
Breakout Session - American Academy of Teachers of Singing
Breakout Session - Authenticity in the Performance of Hall Johnson
NATS Artist Awards (NATSAA)
National Association of Teachers of Singing • 9957 Moorings Drive, Suite 401 • Jacksonville FL 32257 Phone: 904-992-9101 • Fax: 904-262-2587 • Email:
© 1944-2020 National Association of Teachers of Singing, Inc. Reproduction without explicit permission is prohibited. All Rights Reserved.
Privacy Policy | Site Map | Contact Us
Powered by Exware Association Management
